{"test_questions": [[{"question": "A digital logic device used as a buffer should have what input/output characteristics?", "opta": "high input impedance and high output impedance", "optb": "low input impedance and high output impedance", "optc": "low input impedance and low output impedance", "optd": "high input impedance and low output impedance", "ans": "D", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "What is the standard TTL noise margin?", "opta": "5.0 V", "optb": "0.2 V", "optc": "0.8 V", "optd": "0.4 V", "ans": "D", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "The range of a valid LOW input is:", "opta": "0.0 V to 0.4 V", "optb": "0.4 V to 0.8 V", "optc": "0.4 V to 1.8 V", "optd": "0.4 V to 2.4 V", "ans": "B", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "When an IC has two rows of parallel connecting pins, the device is referred to as:", "opta": "a QFP", "optb": "a DIP", "optc": "a phase splitter", "optd": "CMOS", "ans": "B", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "Which digital IC package type makes the most efficient use of printed circuit board space?", "opta": "SMT", "optb": "TO can", "optc": "flat pack", "optd": "DIP", "ans": "A", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "The problem of interfacing IC logic families that have different supply voltages (VCCs) can be solved by using a:", "opta": "level-shifter", "optb": "tri-state shifter", "optc": "translator", "optd": "level-shifter or translator", "ans": "D", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "Ten TTL loads per TTL driver is known as:", "opta": "noise immunity", "optb": "power dissipation", "optc": "fanout", "optd": "propagation delay", "ans": "C", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "Which of the following summarizes the important features of emitter-coupled logic (ECL)?", "opta": "negative voltage operation, high speed, and high power consumption", "optb": "good noise immunity, negative logic, high frequency capability, low power dissipation, and short propagation time", "optc": "slow propagation time, high frequency response, low power consumption, and high output voltage swings", "optd": "poor noise immunity, positive supply voltage operation, good low-frequency operation, and low power", "ans": "A", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "What quantities must be compatible when interfacing two different logic families?", "opta": "only the currents", "optb": "both the voltages and the currents", "optc": "only the voltages", "optd": "both the power dissipation and the impedance", "ans": "B", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "CMOS logic is probably the best all-around circuitry because of its:", "opta": "packing density", "optb": "low power consumption", "optc": "very high noise immunity", "optd": "low power consumption and very high noise immunity", "ans": "D", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "Low power consumption achieved by CMOS circuits is due to which construction characteristic?", "opta": "complementary pairs", "optb": "connecting pads", "optc": "DIP packages", "optd": "small-scale integration", "ans": "A", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "A TTL totem pole circuit is designed so that the output transistors are:", "opta": "always on together", "optb": "providing phase splitting", "optc": "providing voltage regulation", "optd": "never on together", "ans": "D", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "The time needed for an output to change as the result of an input change is known as:", "opta": "noise immunity", "optb": "fanout", "optc": "propagation delay", "optd": "rise time", "ans": "C", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}]]}